grantthornton.co.nz 2019-12-17

# Privacy policy | Grant Thornton

However, you can reset your browser so as to refuse any cookie or to alert you to when a cookie is being sent. Web browsers allow you to control cookies stored on your hard drive through the web browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

We only use cookies to monitor the performance of our website and to improve user experience.

If you choose not to accept our cookies, some of the features of our site may not work as well as we intend.

## Cookies used by the GTIL website

Cookie type | Cookie Name | Purpose  
---|---|---  
Google analytics | utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz | 

These cookies are used to monitor the performance of our site. We use the information to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visits to our site, where visitors have come from to the site and the pages they visited.

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  
Youtube preferences | PREF  
use_hitbox  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE | We use YouTube to embed a selection of videos in our Thinking and campaign pages. The embedded videos do not set cookies themselves and can be played with no cookies set. However, if the 'Share' button is clicked YouTube will set cookies. The VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE cookie attempts to estimate your bandwidth and the use_hitbox and PREF cookies increment the 'views' counter on the YouTube video and stores session preferences. These cookies donâ€™t gather information that identifies a user.  
Twitter | guest_id | We embed a Twitter feed in our Thinking and campaign pages. This cookie is used to identify you to twitter. if you do not have a twitter account or never accessed the twitter.com website directly then twitter will assign you a unique code to track your visit to the Twitter feed.  
  
## How do we use your personal data?

We use your personal data to provide information to you or your organisation.

We may also use your personal data to carry out research about our visitors' demographics, interests and behaviour. We do this to better understand our visitors. This research is compiled and analysed on an aggregated and anonymous basis.

When you give us personal data, those data may be sent electronically to servers anywhere in the world and may be used, stored and processed anywhere in the world.

Whenever and wherever we collect, process or use personal data, we take steps to ensure that it is treated securely and in accordance with our privacy policy.

## To whom might we disclose your personal data?

We may pass your personal data to anyone who needs the data in order to fulfil your request for our services, or process any payment. Some of these may be located outside the European Economic Area.

We may pass your personal data to Grant Thornton member firms or to our data processors.

Except as set out above, we will not disclose your personal information unless we are obliged to do so or allowed to do so, by law, or where we need to do so in order to run our business (for instance where we outsource services or other people process data for us).

## Direct Marketing

You may at any time request us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If you wish to do this, please contact us.

## Links

Our website contains links to Grant Thornton member and correspondent firm websites, but this privacy policy applies only to personal data collected via websites operated by GTIL which include [www.gti.org](http://www.gti.org/ "External link") , [www.internationalbusinessreport.com](http://www.internationalbusinessreport.com/ "External link") and [www.globaldynamismindex.com ](https://www.globaldynamismindex.com/gdi.html "External link - open a new window") and to how GTIL processes personal data. It does not apply to specific member or correspondent firms practising under the Grant Thornton name. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these or other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policy of other sites that collect or use personal data.

## Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed as 100% secure, but we take appropriate steps to try to protect the security of your personal data.

## Contacts

This is the website of GTIL, a non-practicing, non-trading international umbrella organisation that does not deliver services. GTIL and its member firms are not a worldwide partnership.  GTIL and each member firm of GTIL is a separate legal entity.

If you want to request any information about your personal data, please contact us at our registered office.

Registered office address: Grant Thornton House, Melton Street, Euston Square, London NW1 2EP.

## Inaccuracies and Corrections

We would like to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. If you become aware of any errors or inaccuracies please let us know by contacting us at our registered office.
